

CONTACT

Mobile: +49 177 477 8501

E-mail: giorgio.torre8@gmail.com

Location: Munich, Germany

EXPERIENCE

Tenhil GmbH & Co KG

Software Developer January 2023 - current

stellenanzeigen.de

Junior Software Developer June 2021 - December 2022

Bombardier Transportation UK

Project Commercial Manager September 2016 - May 2021

EDUCATION

Cranfield University (UK)

MSc in Manufacturing Systems September 2014 - August 2015

Pisa University (IT)

BSc & MSc in Industrial Engineering September 2010 - August 2014

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English / Italian Native / Bilingual proficiency

German

Professional working proficiency

GIORGIO TORRE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I'm a software developer with a passion for challenges, problemsolving, and delivering projects. I'm a self-starter dedicated to acquiring new skills and honing existing ones. My experiences have forged a strong mix of technical know-how and project delivery acumen, a must in today's fast-paced work world.

SKILLS

- TypeScript / JavaScript
- React / Next.js / Remix.run / Node.js
- HTML5 / CSS3 / Tailwind / Styled Components / SASS
- Redux / Redux Toolkit / RTK Query
- Jest / React Testing Library

PROJECTS

Our Wedding

Stack: Remix / Tailwind / Typescript / Vercel

Fully responsive wedding site to manage RSVP and info sharing with guests - https://www.giorgio-laura.com/ (pwd: Hir3Me!:D)

Personal Portfolio

Stack: Remix / Tailwind / Typescript / Vercel

Fully responsive portfolio app showcasing my work - https://giorgio-portfolio-towerbrother.vercel.app/

Weather App

Stack: React / SASS

SPA weather forecast - data from OpenWeatherAPI - https://towerbrother.github.io/weather-app

JavaScript Calculator

Stack: HTML / CSS / Javascript

Simple, modern-looking calculator coded with Vanilla JS - https://towerbrother.github.io/JS-calculator

LINKS

https://github.com/towerbrother/
https://www.linkedin.com/in/giorgiotorre/